mybabyclothes.com 2016-05-23

# Privacy Policy for The Sanders Team

This privacy policy sets out how “The Sanders Team” uses and protects any information that you give “The Sanders Team” when you use this website. “The Sanders Team” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. “The Sanders Team” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 23/5/2016

**For Everyone, Especially Our Canadian Friends:**  
(CASL) If you wish to register on this website you are giving expressed consent for us to email, call and text message you. If you do not wish for this type of communication please do not register. 

**What we collect:**  
We collect all information from our sign up process. This information is disclosed during the sign up process and can include, name, email, city, state, gender, birthday, picture, website and IP location. 

**What we do with the information:**

We use this information to pass along to an agent to help you find a property. You will be contacted by email, text or phone using this information. Upon registration your information will be shared with our supporting lender.

**Internal record keeping:  
**We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes. We will never sell your information. 

**Security** :  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies** :  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites** :  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information:  
**If you wish to opt out of contact you can click on the unsubscribe link on the bottom of any email correspondence. If you wish to opt out of phone calls please email [support@kunversion.com](mailto:support@kunversion.com).

### Send Us a Message

### Chat with us now!

#### A real live chat operator is online now! We can immediately get your questions answered or make sure we get it to an agent who can.

### About The Sanders Team

The Sanders Team of Keller Williams Realty Partners is one of the fastest growing teams in the Atlanta market. Our commitment to excellence and service is unmatched. It is our goal to leverage leading edge technology, professional and responsive staff, and exceptional customer service to be the top real estate team in the Atlanta area. Our advanced digital media marketing strategies enable us to maximize internet exposure to sell homes fast and for top dollar. Our team always aspires to be the best real estate agents in the Atlanta and Metro-Atlanta area. The Sanders Team specializes in the Metro-Atlanta Georgia real estate market, including Woodstock, Canton, Roswell, Alpharetta, Milton, Marietta, Atlanta, Cumming, Kennesaw, Acworth, Austell, Ball Ground, Dallas, Duluth, Hiram, Holly Springs, Johns Creek, Mableton, Powder Springs, Sandy Springs, Smyrna, Union City, Waleska, and White.  

### Testimonials

"They did a great job of helping us find our new house and an even better job of selling our old house. They stayed within the parameters we had set for our new house, showing only those properties or neighborhoods that met our requirements. They kept us realistic about what we could expect to pay to get what we wanted in a home and local amenities, so we ended up adjusting along the way. When selling our house, they were very knowledgeable about recent sales in our area, along with concessions made for those sales, which helped us set a realistic price and expectations for our sale. They took very good photographs of our house for the listing and made sure our listing had online visibility. When moving, they also provided a list of vendors we could use to either prepare our house for sale, or to assist in getting the new house personalized. They kept us apprised of status and action items all along the way. All communications were timely and detailed, and they were fun and easy to work with. I would definitely recommend this team and would use them again, should the need arise."

### Saved Properties

This is a list of your favorite properties. We will email you if a property is reduced or leaves the market.

**Click 'Save' to add a property to this list.**

### Register / Login

New & returning visitors please enter your information to login.

By clicking 'register' you are agreeing to our terms of use & giving us expressed written consent to contact you.

### Questions? Comments? Complaints?

This message will go directly to the head of our team.

### Location & Address

The Sanders Team  
110 Village Trail, Suite 114  
Woodstock, GA  
__678-929-5283  
__678-426-8770

### Other Locations
